researchpanelasia.com 2018-06-19

# Privacy Policy | dataSpring

Last Updated: February 26, 2018

## Introduction

**dataSpring (“dataSpring” or “our” or “us” or “we” or “dS”) is committed to maintaining the privacy of users to our website (“Clients” “you” “Suppliers” “Contacts”) and to individuals who provide us personal information and data. This privacy policy applies to all websites offered by dataSpring. We refer to those products, services and websites collectively as “Services” in this policy. Although this Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights, it is a statement of dataSpring’s commitment to safeguarding private information.**

**You may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices to[contact@d8aspring.com](mailto:contact@d8aspring.com).**

## Information We Collect

dataSpring conducts online market research studies in numerous countries around the world using online surveys through our Services. We are interested in developing and keeping strong, deep and lasting relationships with all parties that have an interest in our products and services.

In order to operate our website in the most efficient manner, we collect certain data and information through automated means including, IP address, browser type, operating system, referring URLs, information on actions or activities taken or engaged in on our website, and dates and times of website visits. Please refer to our “Cookie Policy” for more information.

Additionally, forms and applications on our website and within our web applications collect personally identifiable information, such as first name, last name, email address, physical address, job title, company name and phone number. By providing such personally identifiable information, you consent to its collection.

dataSpring’s services are not intended for children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, please do not provide personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever on the dataSpring. If you are the parent of a child under 13 and believe your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [contact@d8aspring.com](mailto:contact@d8aspring.com) and we will remove that information.

## How We Use Your Information

We use the information that you provide us via this website and mobile app in the following ways:

  * To process any inquiries raised by you and other communications initiated by you in relation to your dealings with dataSpring and any services provided by the Company;
  * To keep you informed of dataSpring’s products, services and activities;
  * To produce and deliver requested products, services and reports; and
  * To provide requested quotes, panel books and brochures, we require that you provide personally identifiable information (PII) to ensure delivery and execution of your request.

dataSpring does not share or collect personally identifiable information with other third-party organizations for their marketing, advertising or promotional use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We reserve the right to disclose any information that is gathered when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

Any information collected via this website will be treated in the strictest confidence and in accordance with all the pertinent laws and regulations in the countries in which we do business.

## How We Protect Your Personal Information

dataSpring uses reasonable security measures in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control; these include on-line and off-line physical, electronic and managerial safeguards.

dataSpring cannot, however, guarantee protection of all information in all cases. For example, we cannot guarantee protection against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration, or that your information will not be disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

If you have any questions about the security of our website or web applications, you can send an e-mail to [contact@d8aspring.com](mailto:contact@d8aspring.com).

## Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other third party websites. dataSpring is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third party websites.

## Our Cookie Policy

### By using the Service, you consent to the use of cookies.

Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Service, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you.

Cookies can be "session" or "persistent" cookies- see more information on them below.

**How dataSpring uses cookies?**

#### When you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser.

We use cookies for the following purposes: to enable certain functions of the Service, to provide analytics, to store your preferences, to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral advertising.

On our site, we use two kinds of cookies called "session cookie" and "persistent cookie". Session cookies are a temporary cookie stored on your terminal until you close our site. Persistent cookies will remain on your device for a much longer period of time or until you manually delete them (the length of time cookies are stored on your terminal depends on the duration or "lifetime" of the cookie in question).

**Third-party cookies**

In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service, deliver advertisements on and through the Service, and so on.

**What are your choices regarding cookies?**

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

If you use multiple different terminals to access our site (eg computer, smartphone, tablet etc.), each browser on each terminal needs to be adjusted to fit the cookie you want.

Note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.

**Where can you find more information about cookies?**

You can learn more about cookies and the following third-party websites:

  * AllAboutCookies: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>
  * Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Please check this page periodically for changes as dataSpring reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of the Privacy Policy and the website at any time.

Your continued use of the website following the posting of any changes to this Policy will mean that you accept such changes.

## Contact Us

Questions about our Privacy Policy may be emailed to us at [contact@d8aspring.com](mailto:contact@d8aspring.com) or you may send us your questions to:

  * 7F KOSUGI Bldg., Shinjuku 1-28-11, Shinjuku-ku, Tokyo, Japan 160-0022

## Additional Information & Policies

Whether you are a client, prospect, visitor to our website, a user of our mobile app, and/ or a survey respondent, the following additional documentation may apply to your use of our Services:

  * dataSpring Terms of Use: [https://www.d8aspring.com/static/terms](https://www.d8aspring.com/static/terms?hsLang=en-us)
  * surveyon Website Privacy Policy: <https://www.surveyon.com/static/privacy>
  * surveyon Website Terms & Conditions: <http://www.surveyon.com/static/terms>
  * surveyon Mobile App Privacy Policy: <https://www.surveyon.com/mobile_app/privacy>
  * surveyon Mobile App Terms & Conditions: <https://www.surveyon.com/mobile_app/terms>
